

PERSONAL PROFILE

I'm a 30-year-old software developer who loves technology and outdoor sports. Over the past five years, I've been helping companies to achieve their goals developing web applications solutions using javascript tools like ReactJS, React Native, Angular. I'm all about learning new thing every day and building great relationships with my coworkers to continue growing professionally.

SKILLS

- Agile and teamwork oriented
- Frontend developer
- Technologies: Javascript, React, Angular, Typescript, React Native
- adaptable and willing to learn

EDUCATION

Information Systems Engineering - UTN

CONTACT

ramirospinelli92@gmail.com linkedIn/ramiro-spinelli

WORK EXPERIENCE

Kodaris, Senior UX Engineer

www.kodaris.com

OCT 2023 - PRESENT

- Frontend Developer
- Angular
- HTML
- CSS

Sovos, Senior Software Engineer

www.sovos.com

AUG 2017 - JUN 2021 / MAR 2022 - PRESENT

- Full stack developer building web apps with dockerized microservices
- Spring Boot
- React JS
- SQL Server / Oracle

Axioma Studios, Full Stack Developer

www.axiomastudios.com

AUG 2020 -MAY 2022

- Typescript
- Node.js
- Angular 10
- React
- React Native

Lenio Labs, Frontend Developer

www.leniolabs.com

JUN 2021 - SEPT 2021

 Working as a Frontend Developer with a big US client developing Loans web app using Angular and React technologies.

Global Learning, Academic Assistant

www.globalearning.net

SEPT 2020 - SEPT 2021

 Working as academic assistant in the full stack javascript course: